Sections of the Project Report
Students are required to submit a project report as a pdf file, five days before the final semester presentation.
The report should be a typical SWE report with the following sections:
Section1:áRequirements listing and analysis
Section2:áSolution Design and diagrams
Section3:áProject Planning
Section4: Implementation approach
Section 5:áAdopted ethics principles. For this section make sure you have answers for the following questions:
What are the software ethics principles that you adopted?
How did you apply recognized ethics principles? Showing the ethical alternatives and their consequences and which action did you choose?
Clearly mention what documents sources and references you used, and how any license/copyright/legal/privacy are handled?
